Hi! I'm Amit. Learning how to develop Android apps is very exciting.
We assume that you have little or no programming experience.
You'll start with the very basics and move to more intermediate and advanced topics.
You will get off to a quick start by building a simple Crystal Ball app which will teach you how to use Eclipse,
the recommended tool to create android apps,
and you will also learn how to use Java, the programming language to write android apps.
Finally, you will learn how to publish your app to Google Play and the Amazon app store.
Next, we'll increase the complexity by building an app that downloads and displays blogposts from the Treehouse blog.
This project will teach you the design pattern known as model view controller,
how to display a list of data, and how to show a webpage.
You will also learn how to share text with your friends right from within the app.
By the end, you will be comfortable building a fairly complex android app as well as know where to go to continue with your learning.
So join us and good luck!
[Treehouse™]